creditcardchaser.com 2013-04-24

# Privacy Policy

360 Quote LLC is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and have established this privacy statement to disclose our information practices. This privacy statement applies exclusively to the Website, www.CreditCardChaser.com.

### Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Visitors to our Website can browse while remaining completely anonymous. When a user elects to contact us with an inquiry, we collect their name and email information and phone number. We use this collected personal information exclusively to respond to users with information about their inquiry. We do not store this personal information for any other purposes, promotional or otherwise, nor do we share it with third parties for their promotional purposes.

We do not send unsolicited messages to users of our website nor do we store the personal information provided to us on contact forms beyond responding to your inquiry.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, this website uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content. A cookie is a text file containing a unique identifier set on a hard drive by a browser to recognize the user upon return. We do not tie cookies to personal information. We may also employ the use of web beacons in monitoring page views and traffic. A web beacon is a one pixel image embedded within a web page.

We may from time to time employ the use of a third party agent in tracking aggregated non-personal statistical data about our Website users. This third party agent may use cookies or web beacons towards this end. Third party advertisers serving advertisements on the Websites from time to time may also employ the use of cookies in monitoring their ads. We are not responsible for any of these third party cookies, nor do we have access to them.

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

Where necessary, we may disclose information to law enforcement or to other government agencies where a formal request has been made, such as in a civil suit, court order, judicial proceeding or a subpoena.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at our discretion. We shall notify you of any changes made by updating the date on this statement, and we recommend you check back regularly to stay informed of any changes. In the event of a material change to our information practices, we shall notify users by means of a prominent notice on the Website, or by email if we have your contact information.

### Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to our [Contact Us](http://www.creditcardchaser.com/contact/) page for further clarification.

By Mail: 93 S Jackson St, Suite #37960, Seattle, WA 98104-2818

Last updated: December.15.2012
